[
  {
    "question": "Which two traffic types use the Real-Time Transport Protocol (RTP)?",
    "answers": ["video", "voice"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which wireless technology has low-power and data rate requirements making it popular in home automation applications?",
    "answer": "ZigBee"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which layer of the TCP/IP model provides a route to forward messages through an internetwork?",
    "answer": "internet"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which type of server relies on record types such as A, NS, AAAA, and MX in order to provide services?",
    "answer": "DNS"
  },
  {
    "question": "What are proprietary protocols?",
    "answer": "protocols developed by organizations who have control over their definition and operation"
  },
  {
    "question": "What service is provided by DNS?",
    "answer": "Resolves domain names, such as cisco.com, into IP addresses."
  },
  {
    "question": "A client packet is received by a server. The packet has a destination port number of 110. What service is the client requesting?",
    "answer": "POP3"
  },
  {
    "question": "What command can be used on a Windows PC to see the IP configuration of that computer?",
    "answer": "ipconfig"
  },
  {
    "question": "A wired laser printer is attached to a home computer. That printer has been shared so that other computers on the home network can also use the printer. What networking model is in use?",
    "answer": "peer-to-peer (P2P)"
  },
  {
    "question": "What characteristic describes a virus?",
    "answer": "malicious software or code running on an end device"
  },
  {
    "question": "Three bank employees are using the corporate network. The first employee uses a web browser to view a company web page in order to read some announcements. The second employee accesses the corporate database to perform some financial transactions. The third employee participates in an important live audio conference with other corporate managers in branch offices. If QoS is implemented on this network, what will be the priorities from highest to lowest of the different data types?",
    "answer": "audio conference, financial transactions, web page"
  },
  {
    "question": "If Host1 were to transfer a file to the server, what layers of the TCP/IP model would be used?",
    "answer": "application, transport, Internet, and network access layers"
  },
  {
    "question": "The IP address of which device interface should be used as the default gateway setting of host H1?",
    "answer": "R1: G0/0"
  },
  {
    "question": "What service is provided by Internet Messenger?",
    "answer": "An application that allows real-time chatting among remote users."
  },
  {
    "question": "Which protocol was responsible for building the table that is shown?",
    "answer": "ARP"
  },
  {
    "question": "A network administrator notices that some newly installed Ethernet cabling is carrying corrupt and distorted data signals. The new cabling was installed in the ceiling close to fluorescent lights and electrical equipment. Which two factors may interfere with the copper cabling and result in signal distortion and data corruption?",
    "answers": ["RFI", "EMI"]
  },
  {
    "question": "A host is trying to send a packet to a device on a remote LAN segment, but there are currently no mappings in its ARP cache. How will the device obtain a destination MAC address?",
    "answer": "It will send an ARP request for the MAC address of the default gateway."
  },
  {
    "question": "A client packet is received by a server. The packet has a destination port number of 53. What service is the client requesting?",
    "answer": "DNS"
  },
  {
    "question": "A network administrator is adding a new LAN to a branch office. The new LAN must support 25 connected devices. What is the smallest network mask that the network administrator can use for the new network?",
    "answer": "255.255.255.224"
  },
  {
    "question": "What characteristic describes a Trojan horse?",
    "answer": "malicious software or code running on an end device"
  },
  {
    "question": "What service is provided by HTTPS?",
    "answer": "Uses encryption to secure the exchange of text, graphic images, sound, and video on the web."
  },
  {
    "question": "A technician with a PC is using multiple applications while connected to the Internet. How is the PC able to keep track of the data flow between multiple application sessions and have each application receive the correct packet flows?",
    "answer": "The data flow is being tracked based on the source port number that is used by each application."
  },
  {
    "question": "A network administrator is adding a new LAN to a branch office. The new LAN must support 61 connected devices. What is the smallest network mask that the network administrator can use for the new network?",
    "answer": "255.255.255.192"
  },
  {
    "question": "What characteristic describes a DoS attack?",
    "answer": "an attack that slows or crashes a device or network service"
  },
  {
    "question": "What service is provided by SMTP?",
    "answer": "Allows clients to send email to a mail server and the servers to send email to other servers."
  },
  {
    "question": "Which scenario describes a function provided by the transport layer?",
    "answer": "A student has two web browser windows open in order to access two web sites. The transport layer ensures the correct web page is delivered to the correct browser window."
  },
  {
    "question": "Host B on subnet Teachers transmits a packet to host D on subnet Students. Which Layer 2 and Layer 3 addresses are contained in the PDUs that are transmitted from host B to the router?",
    "answers": [
      "Layer 2 destination address = 00-00-0c-94-36-ab",
      "Layer 2 source address = 00-00-0c-94-36-bb",
      "Layer 3 destination address = 172.16.20.200",
      "Layer 3 source address = 172.16.10.200"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What does the term 'attenuation' mean in data communication?",
    "answer": "loss of signal strength as distance increases"
  },
  {
    "question": "An administrator is trying to configure the switch but receives the error message that is displayed in the exhibit. What is the problem?",
    "answer": "The administrator must first enter privileged EXEC mode before issuing the command."
  },
  {
    "question": "Which two protocols operate at the top layer of the TCP/IP protocol suite?",
    "answers": ["POP", "DNS"]
  },
  {
    "question": "A company has a file server that shares a folder named Public. The network security policy specifies that the Public folder is assigned Read-Only rights to anyone who can log into the server while the Edit rights are assigned only to the network admin group. Which component is addressed in the AAA network service framework?",
    "answer": "authorization"
  },
  {
    "question": "What three requirements are defined by the protocols used in network communications to allow message transmission across a network?",
    "answers": ["message size", "message encoding", "delivery options"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What are two characteristics of IP?",
    "answers": ["does not require a dedicated end-to-end connection", "operates independently of the network media"]
  },
  {
    "question": "An employee of a large corporation remotely logs into the company using the appropriate username and password. The employee is attending an important video conference with a customer concerning a large sale. It is important for the video quality to be excellent during the meeting. The employee is unaware that after a successful login, the connection to the company ISP failed. The secondary connection, however, activated within seconds. The disruption was not noticed by the employee or other employees.",
    "answers": ["security", "quality of service", "fault tolerance"]
  },
    {
    "question": "What are two common causes of signal degradation when using UTP cabling?",
    "answers": ["improper termination", "low-quality cable or connectors"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which subnet would include the address 192.168.1.96 as a usable host address?",
    "answer": "192.168.1.64/26"
  },
  {
    "question": "On the basis of the output, which two statements about network connectivity are correct?",
    "answers": [
      "There are 4 hops between this device and the device at 192.168.100.1.",
      "There is connectivity between this device and the device at 192.168.100.1."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which two statements describe how to assess traffic flow patterns and network traffic types using a protocol analyzer?",
    "answers": [
      "Capture traffic during peak utilization times to get a good representation of the different traffic types.",
      "Perform the capture on different network segments."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the consequence of configuring a router with the ipv6 unicast-routing global configuration command?",
    "answer": "The IPv6 enabled router interfaces begin sending ICMPv6 Router Advertisement messages."
  },
  {
    "question": "Which three layers of the OSI model map to the application layer of the TCP/IP model?",
    "answers": ["application", "session", "presentation"]
  },
  {
    "question": "If PC1 is sending a packet to PC2 and routing has been configured between the two routers, what will R1 do with the Ethernet frame header attached by PC1?",
    "answer": "remove the Ethernet header and configure a new Layer 2 header before sending it out S0/0/0"
  },
  {
    "question": "What will happen if the default gateway address is incorrectly configured on a host?",
    "answer": "The host cannot communicate with hosts in other networks."
  },
  {
    "question": "What are two features of ARP?",
    "answers": [
      "If a host is ready to send a packet to a local destination device and it has the IP address but not the MAC address of the destination, it generates an ARP broadcast.",
      "If a device receiving an ARP request has the destination IPv4 address, it responds with an ARP reply."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "A network administrator is adding a new LAN to a branch office. The new LAN must support 90 connected devices. What is the smallest network mask that the network administrator can use for the new network?",
    "answer": "255.255.255.128"
  },
  {
    "question": "What are two ICMPv6 messages that are not present in ICMP for IPv4?",
    "answers": ["Neighbor Solicitation", "Router Advertisement"]
  },
  {
    "question": "A client packet is received by a server. The packet has a destination port number of 80. What service is the client requesting?",
    "answer": "HTTP"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is an advantage for small organizations of adopting IMAP instead of POP?",
    "answer": "Messages are kept in the mail servers until they are manually deleted from the email client."
  },
  {
    "question": "A technician can ping the IP address of the web server of a remote company but cannot successfully ping the URL address of the same web server. Which software utility can the technician use to diagnose the problem?",
    "answer": "nslookup"
  },
  {
    "question": "The global configuration command ip default-gateway 172.16.100.1 is applied to a switch. What is the effect of this command?",
    "answer": "The switch can be remotely managed from a host on another network."
  },
  {
    "question": "What happens when the transport input ssh command is entered on the switch vty lines?",
    "answer": "Communication between the switch and remote users is encrypted."
  },
  {
    "question": "A disgruntled employee is using some free wireless networking tools to determine information about the enterprise wireless networks. This person is planning on using this information to hack the wireless network. What type of attack is this?",
    "answer": "reconnaissance"
  },
  {
    "question": "What service is provided by HTTP?",
    "answer": "A basic set of rules for exchanging text, graphic images, sound, video, and other multimedia files on the web."
  },
  {
    "question": "A client packet is received by a server. The packet has a destination port number of 67. What service is the client requesting?",
    "answer": "DHCP"
  },
  {
    "question": "What are two problems that can be caused by a large number of ARP request and reply messages?",
    "answers": [
      "The ARP request is sent as a broadcast, and will flood the entire subnet.",
      "All ARP request messages must be processed by all nodes on the local network."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which three Windows CLI commands and utilities will provide the necessary information to troubleshoot Internet access?",
    "answers": ["ping", "ipconfig", "nslookup"]
  },
  {
    "question": "During the process of forwarding traffic, what will the router do immediately after matching the destination IP address to a network on a directly connected routing table entry?",
    "answer": "switch the packet to the directly connected interface"
  },
  {
    "question": "What characteristic describes antispyware?",
    "answer": "applications that protect end devices from becoming infected with malicious software"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which access method should be chosen to keep user ID, password, and session contents private during remote CLI connectivity?",
    "answer": "SSH"
  },
  {
    "question": "What are the two most effective ways to defend against malware?",
    "answers": [
      "Update the operating system and other application software.",
      "Install and update antivirus software."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which type of security threat would be responsible if a spreadsheet add-on disables the local software firewall?",
    "answer": "Trojan horse"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which frame field is used by a destination node to ensure that a transmitted data signal has not been altered?",
    "answer": "frame check sequence field"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the smallest network mask that can support 4 connected devices?",
    "answer": "255.255.255.248"
  },
  {
    "question": "What service is provided by POP3?",
    "answer": "Retrieves email from the server by downloading the email to the local mail application of the client."
  },
  {
    "question": "What two security solutions are most likely to be used only in a corporate environment?",
    "answers": ["virtual private networks", "intrusion prevention systems"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What characteristic describes antivirus software?",
    "answer": "applications that protect end devices from becoming infected with malicious software"
  },
  {
    "question": "What mechanism is used by a router to prevent a received IPv4 packet from traveling endlessly on a network?",
    "answer": "It decrements the value of the TTL field by 1 and if the result is 0, it discards the packet and sends a Time Exceeded message to the source host."
  },
  {
    "question": "A client packet is received by a server. The packet has a destination port number of 69. What service is the client requesting?",
    "answer": "TFTP"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which three additional steps are required to configure R1 to accept only encrypted SSH connections?",
    "answers": [
      "Configure the IP domain name on the router.",
      "Generate the SSH keys.",
      "Enable inbound vty SSH sessions."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "An IPv6 enabled device sends a data packet with the destination address of FF02::2. What is the target of this packet?",
    "answer": "all IPv6 configured routers on the local link"
  },
  {
    "question": "What are the three parts of an IPv6 global unicast address?",
    "answers": ["subnet ID", "global routing prefix", "interface ID"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which three areas of concern should be accounted for when building a wireless network?",
    "answers": ["interference", "security", "coverage area"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the fastest way a network administrator could test whether the banner is properly configured?",
    "answer": "Exit privileged EXEC mode and press Enter."
  },
  {
    "question": "What method is used to manage contention-based access on a wireless network?",
    "answer": "CSMA/CA"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is a function of the data link layer?",
    "answer": "provides for the exchange of frames over a common local media"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the purpose of the TCP sliding window?",
    "answer": "to request that a source decrease the rate at which it transmits data"
  },
  {
    "question": "What characteristic describes spyware?",
    "answer": "software that is installed on a user device and collects information about the user"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which switching method drops frames that fail the FCS check?",
    "answer": "store-and-forward switching"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which range of link-local addresses can be assigned to an IPv6-enabled interface?",
    "answer": "FE80::/10"
  },
  {
    "question": "What service is provided by FTP?",
    "answer": "Allows for data transfers between a client and a file server."
  },
  {
    "question": "Which two configuration values must be set on the host to access http://www.cisco.com/?",
    "answers": ["DNS server", "default gateway"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which two statements accurately describe an advantage or a disadvantage when deploying NAT for IPv4?",
    "answers": [
      "NAT introduces problems for some applications that require end-to-end connectivity.",
      "NAT provides a solution to slow down the IPv4 address depletion."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What would be the interface ID of an IPv6 enabled interface with a MAC address of 1C-6F-65-C2-BD-F8 when the interface ID is generated by using the EUI-64 process?",
    "answer": "1E6F:65FF:FEC2:BDF8"
  },
  {
    "question": "PC1 issues an ARP request because it needs to send a packet to PC2. What will happen next?",
    "answer": "PC2 will send an ARP reply with the PC2 MAC address."
  },
  {
    "question": "What service is provided by BOOTP?",
    "answer": "Legacy application that enables a diskless workstation to discover its own IP address and find a BOOTP server on the network."
  },
  {
    "question": "What characteristic describes adware?",
    "answer": "software that is installed on a user device and collects information about the user"
  },
  {
    "question": "To which switching method will the switch revert when a user-defined error threshold is reached?",
    "answer": "store-and-forward"
  },
  {
    "question": "What are two primary responsibilities of the Ethernet MAC sublayer?",
    "answers": ["accessing the media", "data encapsulation"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What three facts can be determined from the viewable output of the show ip interface brief command?",
    "answers": [
      "The switch can be remotely managed.",
      "One device is attached to a physical interface.",
      "The default SVI has been configured."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the subnet ID associated with the IPv6 address 2001:DA48:FC5:A4:3D1B::1/64?",
    "answer": "2001:DA48:FC5:A4::/64"
  },
  {
    "question": "Users are reporting longer delays in authentication and in accessing network resources during certain time periods of the week. What kind of information should network engineers check to find out if this situation is part of a normal network behavior?",
    "answer": "the network performance baseline"
  },
  {
    "question": "How does the service password-encryption command enhance password security on Cisco routers and switches?",
    "answer": "It encrypts passwords that are stored in router or switch configuration files."
  },
  {
    "question": "Which two statements are correct in a comparison of IPv4 and IPv6 packet headers? (Choose two.)",
    "answers": [
      "The Source Address field name from IPv4 is kept in IPv6.",
      "The Time-to-Live field from IPv4 has been replaced by the Hop Limit field in IPv6."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "A network administrator wants to have the same network mask for all networks at a particular small site. The site has the following networks and number of devices: IP phones – 22 addresses, PCs – 20 addresses needed, Printers – 2 addresses needed, Scanners – 2 addresses needed",
    "answer": "255.255.255.224"
  },
  {
    "question": "What characteristic describes identity theft?",
    "answer": "the use of stolen credentials to access private data"
  },
  {
    "question": "A network administrator is adding a new LAN to a branch office. The new LAN must support 200 connected devices. What is the smallest network mask that the network administrator can use for the new network?",
    "answer": "255.255.255.0"
  },
  {
    "question": "What are three commonly followed standards for constructing and installing cabling? (Choose three.)",
    "answers": [
      "cable lengths",
      "pinouts",
      "connector types"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Refer to the exhibit. What is wrong with the displayed termination?",
    "answer": "The untwisted length of each wire is too long."
  },
  {
    "question": "A client packet is received by a server. The packet has a destination port number of 143. What service is the client requesting?",
    "answer": "IMAP"
  },
  {
    "question": "What are two characteristics shared by TCP and UDP? (Choose two.)",
    "answers": [
      "port numbering",
      "use of checksum"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Refer to the exhibit. Which two network addresses can be assigned to the network containing 10 hosts? Your answers should waste the fewest addresses, not reuse addresses that are already assigned, and stay within the 10.18.10.0/24 range of addresses. (Choose two.)",
    "answers": [
      "10.18.10.208/28",
      "10.18.10.224/28"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "A client packet is received by a server. The packet has a destination port number of 21. What service is the client requesting?",
    "answer": "FTP"
  },
  {
    "question": "What attribute of a NIC would place it at the data link layer of the OSI model?",
    "answer": "MAC address"
  },
  {
    "question": "A network administrator is adding a new LAN to a branch office. The new LAN must support 10 connected devices. What is the smallest network mask that the network administrator can use for the new network?",
    "answer": "255.255.255.240"
  },
  {
    "question": "What technique is used with UTP cable to help protect against signal interference from crosstalk?",
    "answer": "twisting the wires together into pairs"
  },
  {
    "question": "Refer to the exhibit. The network administrator has assigned the LAN of LBMISS an address range of 192.168.10.0. This address range has been subnetted using a /29 prefix. In order to accommodate a new building, the technician has decided to use the fifth subnet for configuring the new network (subnet zero is the first subnet). By company policies, the router interface is always assigned the first usable host address and the workgroup server is given the last usable host address. Which configuration should be entered into the properties of the workgroup server to allow connectivity to the Internet?",
    "answer": "IP address: 192.168.10.38 subnet mask: 255.255.255.248, default gateway: 192.168.10.33"
  },
  {
    "question": "Refer to the exhibit. The switches are in their default configuration. Host A needs to communicate with host D, but host A does not have the MAC address for its default gateway. Which network hosts will receive the ARP request sent by host A?",
    "answer": "only hosts B, C, and router R1"
  },
  {
    "question": "Refer to the exhibit. A network engineer has been given the network address of 192.168.99.0 and a subnet mask of 255.255.255.192 to subnet across the four networks shown. How many total host addresses are unused across all four subnets?",
    "answer": "200"
  },
  {
    "question": "A client packet is received by a server. The packet has a destination port number of 22. What service is the client requesting?",
    "answer": "SSH"
  },
  {
    "question": "What characteristic describes an IPS?",
    "answer": "a network device that filters access and traffic coming into a network"
  },
  {
    "question": "What service is provided by DHCP?",
    "answer": "Dynamically assigns IP addresses to end and intermediary devices."
  },
  {
    "question": "Refer to the exhibit. The switches have a default configuration. Host A needs to communicate with host D, but host A does not have the MAC address for the default gateway. Which network devices will receive the ARP request sent by host A?",
    "answer": "only hosts B, C, and router R1"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which wireless technology has low-power and low-data rate requirements making it popular in IoT environments?",
    "answer": "Zigbee"
  },
  {
    "question": "What two ICMPv6 message types must be permitted through IPv6 access control lists to allow resolution of Layer 3 addresses to Layer 2 MAC addresses? (Choose two.)",
    "answers": [
      "neighbor solicitations",
      "neighbor advertisements"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "A client is using SLAAC to obtain an IPv6 address for its interface. After an address has been generated and applied to the interface, what must the client do before it can begin to use this IPv6 address?",
    "answer": "It must send an ICMPv6 Neighbor Solicitation message to ensure that the address is not already in use on the network."
  },
  {
    "question": "Two pings were issued from a host on a local network. The first ping was issued to the IP address of the default gateway of the host and it failed. The second ping was issued to the IP address of a host outside the local network and it was successful. What is a possible cause for the failed ping?",
    "answer": "Security rules are applied to the default gateway device, preventing it from processing ping requests."
  },
  {
    "question": "An organization is assigned an IPv6 address block of 2001:db8:0:ca00::/56. How many subnets can be created without using bits in the interface ID space?",
    "answer": "256"
  },
  {
    "question": "What subnet mask is needed if an IPv4 network has 40 devices that need IP addresses and address space is not to be wasted?",
    "answer": "255.255.255.192"
  },
  {
    "question": "Refer to the exhibit. If host A sends an IP packet to host B, what will the destination address be in the frame when it leaves host A?",
    "answer": "BB:BB:BB:BB:BB:BB"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is a benefit of using cloud computing in networking?",
    "answer": "Network capabilities are extended without requiring investment in new infrastructure, personnel, or software."
  },
  {
    "question": "Which two statements are correct about MAC and IP addresses during data transmission if NAT is not involved? (Choose two.)",
    "answers": [
      "Destination IP addresses in a packet header remain constant along the entire path to a target host.",
      "Destination and source MAC addresses have local significance and change every time a frame goes from one LAN to another."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is one main characteristic of the data link layer?",
    "answer": "It shields the upper layer protocol from being aware of the physical medium to be used in the communication."
  },
  {
    "question": "What are three characteristics of the CSMA/CD process? (Choose three.)",
    "answers": [
      "A device listens and waits until the media is not busy before transmitting.",
      "After detecting a collision, hosts can attempt to resume transmission after a random time delay has expired.",
      "All of the devices on a segment see data that passes on the network medium."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which information does the show startup-config command display?",
    "answer": "the contents of the saved configuration file in the NVRAM"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which two commands can be used on a Windows host to display the routing table? (Choose two.)",
    "answers": [
      "route print",
      "netstat -r"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What are two functions that are provided by the network layer? (Choose two.)",
    "answers": [
      "directing data packets to destination hosts on other networks",
      "providing end devices with a unique network identifier"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What characteristic describes a VPN?",
    "answer": "a tunneling protocol that provides remote users with secure access into the network of an organization"
  },
  {
    "question": "Why would a Layer 2 switch need an IP address?",
    "answer": "to enable the switch to be managed remotely"
  },
  {
    "question": "A user sends an HTTP request to a web server on a remote network. During encapsulation for this request, what information is added to the address field of a frame to indicate the destination?",
    "answer": "the MAC address of the default gateway"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is an advantage to using a protocol that is defined by an open standard?",
    "answer": "It encourages competition and promotes choices."
  },
  {
    "question": "Data is being sent from a source PC to a destination server. Which three statements correctly describe the function of TCP or UDP in this situation? (Choose three.)",
    "answers": [
      "The source port field identifies the running application or service that will handle data returning to the PC.",
      "UDP segments are encapsulated within IP packets for transport across the network.",
      "The UDP destination port number identifies the application or service on the server which will handle the data."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Refer to the exhibit. A company uses the address block of 128.107.0.0/16 for its network. What subnet mask would provide the maximum number of equal size subnets while providing enough host addresses for each subnet in the exhibit?",
    "answer": "255.255.255.128"
  },
  {
    "question": "A network administrator wants to have the same subnet mask for three subnetworks at a small site. The site has the following networks and numbers of devices:",
    "answer": "255.255.255.240"
  },
  {
    "question": "What two pieces of information are displayed in the output of the show ip interface brief command? (Choose two.)",
    "answers": [
      "IP addresses",
      "Layer 1 statuses"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "A user is complaining that an external web page is taking longer than normal to load.The web page does eventually load on the user machine. Which tool should the technician use with administrator privileges in order to locate where the issue is in the network?",
    "answer": "tracert"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which value, that is contained in an IPv4 header field, is decremented by each router that receives a packet?",
    "answer": "Time-to-Live"
  },
  {
    "question": "A network technician is researching the use of fiber optic cabling in a new technology center. Which two issues should be considered before implementing fiber optic media? (Choose two.)",
    "answers": [
      "Fiber optic cabling requires different termination and splicing expertise from what copper cabling requires.",
      "Fiber optic provides higher data capacity but is more expensive than copper cabling."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "A user is executing a tracert to a remote device. At what point would a router, which is in the path to the destination device, stop forwarding the packet?",
    "answer": "when the value in the TTL field reaches zero"
  },
  {
    "question": "Users report that the network access is slow. After questioning the employees, the network administrator learned that one employee downloaded a third-party scanning program for the printer. What type of malware might be introduced that causes slow performance of the network?",
    "answer": "worm"
  }
]

